<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    tools:context="com.example.gajanan.presidentsofindia.Fragment_PratibhaDeviSinghPatil">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="vertical">

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="200dp"
            android:id="@+id/img_sarvepalliRadhakrishnan"
            android:layout_gravity="center_horizontal"
            android:src="@mipmap/sarvepalliradhakrishnan"/>

        <TextView
            android:layout_weight="1"
            android:gravity="center"
            android:textSize="16sp"
            android:textColor="#fff"
            android:layout_marginTop="5dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"
            android:background="#000"
            android:layout_gravity="center"
            android:text="Term of Office: 13 May, 1962 to 13 May, 1967"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"/>


    </LinearLayout>
    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:scrollbars="vertical"
        android:fillViewport="true">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:id="@+id/txt_sarvepalliRadhakrishnan"
            android:layout_marginTop="5dp"
            android:textSize="18sp"
            android:textColor="#fff"
            android:background="#000"
            android:gravity="center"
            android:text="Sarvepalli Radhakrishnan (5 September 1888 – 17 April 1975) was an Indian philosopher and statesman who served as the first Vice President of India (1952–1962) and the second President of India (1962–1967) \n One of India's most distinguished twentieth-century scholars of comparative religion and philosophy,after completing his education at Madras Christian College in 1911, he became Assistant Professor and later Professor of Philosophy at Madras Presidency College then subsequently Professor of Philosophy at the University of Mysore (1918-1921); the King George V Chair of Mental and Moral Science at the University of Calcutta (1921–1932) and Spalding Professor of Eastern Religion and Ethics at University of Oxford (1936–1952) by which he became the first Indian to hold a professorial chair at the University of Oxford. He was Upton Lecturer at Manchester College, Oxford in 1926, 1929, and 1930. In 1930 he was appointed Haskell lecturer in Comparative Religion at the University of Chicago.\n Radhakrishnan was awarded several high awards during his life, including a knighthood in 1931, the Bharat Ratna, the highest civilian award in India, in 1954, and honorary membership of the British Royal Order of Merit in 1963. He was also one of the founders of Helpage India, a non profit organisation for elderly underprivileged in India. Radhakrishnan believed that 'teachers should be the best minds in the country'. Since 1962, his birthday has been celebrated in India as Teachers' Day on 5 September every year "
            android:layout_weight="1.0"/>
    </ScrollView>
</LinearLayout>
